So, let's go on, let's continue and move on to video generation.
So, in the video part, as you see, again, we have plenty of models available over here
that we can choose from, and we can choose motion control, so it's a started creation
with the optimized settings, Taylor, for various design intents, so this is the type
of motion that I want my video to have, and we also have motion elements, right, so these
are all selectable, selectable over here.
What else do we have?
We have prompt in hands, which is by default set to O2, and we have style.
We can choose from the vibes, so it can either be a logo, for example, when it comes to
logo motion generation with, you know, Leonardo, or clay, pro photo, you know, paper craft,
all of these are available as well, the vibe.
What else, the lighting, the color theme, you know, all of them are crucible, and the generation
mode, which can either be fast, which generates us a 480p video, and we can also be generating
using the quality option, which is for HD generation, you know, and we have video dimensions,
we have number of videos, and all of them, and all of them are available.
As you see, we can still have image references, and we also can add up a prompt over here,
so this is pretty much the same with what we have with image generation with Leonardo.